{
    "id": "56405e42149c46ed8dcf934fd8b67e88",
    "title": "Join the sentences with a conjunction",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f8347a83d0ac4c73aab03f49ebcd0f37",
            "title": "Join Sentences With Conjunctions",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "She is pretty ............................. intelligent.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as well",
                        "as well as",
                        "both"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He is greedy .......................................... dishonest.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as well as",
                        "as well",
                        "both"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "God made small things ............................................ great things.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as well as",
                        "as well",
                        "both"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Neither Martin ................................................ his father is tall.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "or",
                        "nor"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is .......................................... honest nor hard working.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "neither",
                        "nor",
                        "either"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "................................................ they gave her the best treatment, they could not save her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "However",
                        "In spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "............................................ she had the qualifications, she did not get the job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Although",
                        "However",
                        "In spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was ill ........................................... he attended the meeting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "but",
                        "though",
                        "however"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "........................................... the lawyer defended his client very well, he lost the case.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However",
                        "In spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": ".......................................... he is not educated, he possesses practical wisdom.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "However",
                        "In spite of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}